[
    {
        "front": "Mother (mine)",
        "back": "Haha",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Father (mine)",
        "back": "Chichi",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Younger Sister (mine)",
        "back": "Imōto",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Elder Sister (mine)",
        "back": "Ane",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Younger Brother (mine)",
        "back": "Otōto",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Elder Brother (mine)",
        "back": "Ani",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Grandmother (mine)",
        "back": "Sobo",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Grandfather (mine)",
        "back": "Sofu",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Wife (mine) ",
        "back": "Tsuma",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Husband (mine)",
        "back": "Otto",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Daughter (mine)",
        "back": "Musume",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Son (mine)",
        "back": "Musuko",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Mother (someone else)",
        "back": "Okōsan",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Father (someone else)",
        "back": "Otōsan",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Younger Sister (someone else)",
        "back": "Imōto",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Elder Sister (someone else)",
        "back": "One-San",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Younger Brother (someone else)",
        "back": "Otōto",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Elder Brother (someone else)",
        "back": "Oni-San",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Grandmother (someone else)",
        "back": "Obāsan",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Grandfather (someone else)",
        "back": "Ojīsan",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Wife (someone else)",
        "back": "Okusan",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Husband  (someone else)",
        "back": "Goshujin",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Daughter (someone else)",
        "back": "Musumesan",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Son (someone else)",
        "back": "Musukosan",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Ringo ",
        "back": "Apple",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Ichigo ",
        "back": "Strawberry",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Momo",
        "back": "Peach",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Suika",
        "back": "Watermelon",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Mikan",
        "back": "(Japanese) Orange",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Budō",
        "back": "Grape",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Nashi",
        "back": "Japanese Pear",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kaki",
        "back": "Persimmon",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Banana",
        "back": "Banana",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Meron",
        "back": "Melon",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Lemon",
        "back": "Remon",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kami",
        "back": "Hair",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Atama",
        "back": "Head",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Me",
        "back": "Eyes",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Mimi",
        "back": "Ears",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Hana",
        "back": "Nose",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kuchi",
        "back": "Mouth",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kao",
        "back": "Face",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kata",
        "back": "Shoulders",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Ude",
        "back": "Hands",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Ashi",
        "back": "Legs",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Onaka",
        "back": "Stomach",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Te",
        "back": "Hand, arm",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Ha",
        "back": "Teeth",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kuruma",
        "back": "Car",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Densha",
        "back": "Train",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Jitensha",
        "back": "Cycle",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Eki",
        "back": "Station",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Basu tei",
        "back": "Bus Stop",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Chikatetsu",
        "back": "Subway",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Mise",
        "back": "Shop",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Gakkō",
        "back": "School",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Ginkō",
        "back": "Bank",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Byōin",
        "back": "Hospital",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Ie",
        "back": "House",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Uchi",
        "back": "Home",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kōen",
        "back": "Park",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kyōshitsu",
        "back": "Classroom",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Gakusei",
        "back": "Student",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Shōgakkō",
        "back": "Primary",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Chūgakko",
        "back": "Middle",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kōkō",
        "back": "High School",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Daigaku",
        "back": "University",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Tomodachi",
        "back": "Friends",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Gohan",
        "back": "Food",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Last Year",
        "back": "Kyonen",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "This Year",
        "back": "Kotoshi",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Next Year",
        "back": "Rainen",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Last  Month",
        "back": "Sengetsu",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "This Month",
        "back": "Kongetsu",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Next Month",
        "back": "Raigetsu",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Last Week",
        "back": "Senshū",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "This Week",
        "back": "Konshū",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Next Week",
        "back": "Raishū",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Nichiyōbi",
        "back": "Sunday",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Getsuyōbi",
        "back": "Monday",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kayōbi",
        "back": "Tuesday",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Suiyōbi",
        "back": "Wednesday",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Mokuyōbi",
        "back": "Thursday",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kinyōbi",
        "back": "Friday",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Doyōbi",
        "back": "Saturday",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Nan, Nani",
        "back": "What",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Doko / Dochira",
        "back": "Where",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Dare / Donata",
        "back": "Who",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Dōshite / Naze",
        "back": "Why",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Doyatte / Nande",
        "back": "How",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Itsu",
        "back": "When",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Ikura",
        "back": "How Much",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Oikutsu",
        "back": "How Old",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Dore / Dono",
        "back": "Which",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Jagaimo",
        "back": "Potato",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Tomato",
        "back": "Tomato",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Tamanegi",
        "back": "Onion",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Daikon",
        "back": "(Japanese) Raddish",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Ninjin",
        "back": "Carrot",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kyabetsu",
        "back": "Cabbage",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kyūri",
        "back": "Cucumber",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Mame",
        "back": "Beans, Peas",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Retasu",
        "back": "Lettuce",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Hakusai",
        "back": "Chinese Cabbage",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Hōrensō",
        "back": "Spinach",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Nasu",
        "back": "Egg plant, Brinjal",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Negi",
        "back": "Welsh Onion",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Amai",
        "back": "Sweet",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Karai",
        "back": "Spicy",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Sappai",
        "back": "Salty",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Suppoi",
        "back": "Sour",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Nigai",
        "back": "Bitter",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Umai",
        "back": "Tasty",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Samui",
        "back": "Cold (Atmos.)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Tsumetai",
        "back": "Cold (Obj.)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Atsui",
        "back": "Hot",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Nihon",
        "back": "Japan",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Indo",
        "back": "India",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Chūgoku",
        "back": "China",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kankoku",
        "back": "Korea",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Roshia",
        "back": "Russia",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Amerika",
        "back": "America",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Igirisu",
        "back": "England",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Itaria",
        "back": "Italy",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Doitsu",
        "back": "Germany",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Tai",
        "back": "Thailand",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Furansu",
        "back": "France",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Burajiru",
        "back": "Brazil",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Sushi",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Okonomiyaki",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Sashimi",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Teishoku",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Tempura",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Udon",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Soba",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Onigiri",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Gyōza",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Miso",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Yakiniku",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Takoyaki",
        "back": "(Dish)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Mizu",
        "back": "Water",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kōhii",
        "back": "Coffee",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kōcha",
        "back": "Black Tea",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "(O)cha",
        "back": "Green Tea",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Jūsu",
        "back": "Juice",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Miruku / Gyūnyū",
        "back": "Milk",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Biiru",
        "back": "Beer",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Wain",
        "back": "Wine",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Osake",
        "back": "Alcohol",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Hikōki",
        "back": "Airplane",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kuruma",
        "back": "Car",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Bicycle",
        "back": "Jitensha",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Baiku",
        "back": "Bike",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Torakku",
        "back": "Truck",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Chikatetsu",
        "back": "Underground train",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Metoro",
        "back": "Metro",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Densha",
        "back": "Electric train",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Fune",
        "back": "Ship",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Takushi",
        "back": "Taxi",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Bullet Train",
        "back": "Shinkansen",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Tōkyō",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Ōsaka",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kyōto",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kōbe",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Nagoya",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Yokohama",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Fukuoka",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Shizuoka",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Sendai",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Fukushima",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    },
    {
        "front": "Kanazawa",
        "back": "(Major Cities)",
        "chapter": "Additional"
    }
]